{
    "id": "a4adea4f2ccd41f78332b25eb09bcd15",
    "title": "Present or past participle quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………. with milk and sugar, it makes a delicious breakfast.",
            "description": "The complete sentence is 'When it is served with milk and sugar....'",
            "answers": [
                "Served",
                "Serving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "56e201e7bd1a4122a00594294c24fa6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Most of the people ……………… to the party were neighbors.",
            "description": "The complete sentence is 'Most of the people who were invited to the party...'",
            "answers": [
                "invited",
                "inviting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "39750102de4c4cada8f36db921df8319"
        },
        {
            "question": "Not ………………. what to do, I called the doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knowing",
                "known"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a71aa7ed3e64d7a8ad8bcc2016ad621"
        },
        {
            "question": "The people ...................... have been informed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "concerned",
                "concerning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33f3e2feff8544a2bbf64f0591349498"
        },
        {
            "question": "The professor is …………………. by his students.",
            "description": "This is a passive construction and it is constructed with a past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "admiring",
                "admired"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8a849adc2e864fac8f324a5b51015e8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ………………….. by the way she spoke to me.",
            "description": "We make passive constructions with past participles.",
            "answers": [
                "annoying",
                "annoyed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b73f49388c1845dd911c87a09b5f7197"
        },
        {
            "question": "I found her sitting at a table ……………… with papers.",
            "description": "The complete sentence is 'I found her sitting at a table that was covered with papers'.",
            "answers": [
                "covering",
                "covered"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a633a4fb6db44f2289c5427eda47c8e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was very ..................... by her performance.",
            "description": "We make passive constructions with past participle forms.",
            "answers": [
                "amused",
                "amusing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "896fbea389ab41978bcb7869b55bca7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her performance was really ………………..",
            "description": "Ing forms are used to make present and past continuous tense forms.",
            "answers": [
                "amusing",
                "amused"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2a93c6caa6df49d5ad070157f02f0acd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The first runner came in closely ………………….. by the second.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "following",
                "followed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "01f4d260764744c28cbe1e1310b5c94f"
        }
    ]
}